ANTHONY AROSTEGUI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Phone: (+51) 992-830-942

Email: anthony.arostegui@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /in/anthonyarostegui

Github: @anargu

ABOUT ME

Software developer with 5 years of full-stack experience developing, designing and enhancing software solutions and research scientific projects. Passionate about science, new technologies, and innovation in computer vision projects. Experience developing and implementing augmented reality projects.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Internship at Silicon Valley, Intel & Google - 2016 Winner at Belatrix's Hackathon - 2016 Honored at SNMPE's Hackathon - 2016 Winner at UTEC's Hackathon - 2015

COMPLEMENTARY KNOWLEDGE

Coursera & deeplearning.ai

Deep Learning Specialization, 2020

Global StartUp Lab Bootcamp Program

Massachusetts Institute of Technology - UTEC, 2016

Centro de Idiomas de la Universidad del Pacífico

English advanced program, 2015

Residence in Network of Open Technologies for Science, Education and Research - CYTED

Internship at Universidade Federal do Rio Grande do Sul, Porto Alegre, Brasil, July 2019

PUBLICATIONS

- Bueno JC., Farfán J., De la Puente J., Peña L., Arce C., Aróstegui A., Malpartida B., Valdivia J., PérezLu J., Egoavil M., Cóndor D., Pinazo M. & Quezada J. (2018) **Telemedicine in Palliative Care: An Application which helps Caregivers and Medical Staff.** Revista I+i Investigación Aplicada e Innovación Vol. 12, pp 17-25.

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

UPCH - UTEC

Telemedicine in Palliative Care: An Application which helps Caregivers and Medical Staff (2017)

- Research project financed by CONCYTEC.
- A Web platform that allow doctors and caregivers to monitor and attend patients with palliative care.
- Analysed the digital solutions.
- Developed the web platform of the project.

UTEC

Thesis: Assessment of awareness and engagement in Advertising with Augmented Reality (AR) (2017)

- Evaluation of Advertising with AR against traditional Advertising. Educational Campaign Ad with AR consisting in an app and QR Points in different areas of the university.
- Organized and designed the experiment in the university.
- Acquired budget and permission from the university to develop the experiment.
- Designed and developed the AR application for Android.

Mobile AR App for Calculus students (2014)

- Assessed the effectiveness of an AR app as an educational tool to learn 3D geometries in Calculus course.
- Developed the AR application with Unity And Vuforia.
- Organized and presented the investigation at VLI (Vive La Ingeniería) fair in UTEC.

Mobile AR App for Retail Clothing (2014)

- Developed the AR application with Unity And Vuforia.
- 3D modeled of products to be shown in magazines

HSEAS - UTEC

Harvard School of Engineering and Applied Sciences Program: Design of a water filter for communities (2013)

- Designed a functional prototype of a water filter accessible by low resources communities.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSIDAD DE INGENIERIA Y TECNOLOGIA

Bachelor degree in Industrial Engineering with specialization in Information and Technology (IT), 2017

- Top fourth in my career.

TECH SKILLS

EXPERT

Languages: Vue, Dart, JS, Python, Golang, SQL, Java. **Frameworks/SDK:** Flutter, Android,

Docker, Processing, p5.js.

PROEFICIENT

Languages: C, C#, R, Octave. **Frameworks/SDK:** Kubernetes, MongoDB, Tensorflow, Keras, Jupyter, ArKit, ARCore, Vuforia, ARToolKit, Arduino, Unity. **Cloud Services:** Firebase,

DigitalOcean, AWS.

ENTHUSIAST

Languages: Rust, iOS (Swift).

PROJECTS

Prilei

CTO & Software Developer (2017 - Present)

- Prllel: Augmented Reality Social Platform for sharing stories in real places.
- Design and development of Backend side, DB modeling.
- UI/UX Design and development of Frontend side with ARCore (Android) and ARKit (iOS).

WORK EXPERIENCE

backend with Firebase.

UPCH

Software Developer (September 2020 - Present)

- Resp IoT: IoT system for remote monitoring of vital signs in COVID patients. Project Winner at Engineering X Pandemic Preparedness.

- Development and design of a PWA (Progressive Web Application) and

BBVA

Tech Leader (2020 - Present)

- Leading a team as Kanban master for development of new security features following Agile methodology. Achievement of SDK implementation and 3rd party libraries for the new branded BBVA app.
- Coordination with the BBVA Global teams (México and Spain).

Mobile Channels Specialist (2018 - Present)

- Development of new features and continues improving in BBVA app.

Voz 3D

Frontend Developer (2017 - 2018)

- Voz 3D: Platform that translates from text or voice speech to a sign languaje representend by a 3D gestual animation.
- PWA (Progressive Web Application) design and development. Stack: Firebase, Three.js (WEB GL).

Bombo

Co-Founder (2017 - Present)

- Bombo: First Fantasy in Perú. Winner at StartUp Perú 7G.

Frontend Developer (2017 - 2018)

- Development and Design of PWA (Progressive Web Application). Stack: Vue.js, Polymer y Lit-html.